<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>The National Radio Company of Ukraine</title>
<link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/</link>
<description>nrcu.gov.ua - news and publications</description>
<copyright>Copyright 2012 - The National Radio Company of Ukraine</copyright>
<language>uk-UK</language>
<image>
<url>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/rss/button.gif</url><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/</link><title>www.nrcu.gov.ua</title>
</image>
<lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 12:06:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
<category domain="http://www.nrcu.gov.ua">News</category> 
<generator>NRCU (rss 2.0)</generator>
<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs> 
<ttl>600</ttl>
<item><title>Ukraine, EU start high-level dialogue on environmental issues</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175840</link><description>Such agreement was reached at a meeting between Ukrainian Environment and Natural Resources Minister Eduard Stavytsky and European Commissioner for Environment Janez Potocnik.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 12:06:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Government to hold special meeting devoted to road safety</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175835</link><description>This was voiced by Prime Minister Mykola Azarov during his meeting  with representatives of public community organizations in the field of road safety.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 11:41:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category><enclosure url="http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/_picture/parent/listing/176/148_175835.jpg" length="8752" type="image/jpeg" /></item>
<item><title>Children of miners with 15 year underground work record to be addmitted to universities by state and local budgets</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175834</link><description>President Viktor Yanukovych signed a law which authorized admission to the university by the state and local budgets of children of miners who have worked underground work at least 15 years.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 10:42:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Government to widely involve public community organizations in providing social services</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175831</link><description>This was announced by Ukrainian Deputy Prime Minister and Social Policy Minister Serhiy Tihipko at a meeting of the board of the Ministry of Social Policy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 10:28:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category><enclosure url="http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/_picture/parent/listing/176/148_175831.jpg" length="13147" type="image/jpeg" /></item>
<item><title>Kyiv City Council Secretary asks parliament to set date for early mayoral election in Kyiv</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175828</link><description>Deputy Kyiv Mayor and Kyiv City Council Secretary Halyna Hereha, who currently fulfils the duties of the city mayor, has filed a petition to the Verkhovna Rada on setting the date for the holding of an early mayoral election in Kyiv.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 10:07:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Ukraine resumes cooperation with EU on sale of emission quotas</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175827</link><description>Ukrainian Environment and Natural Resources Minister Eduard Stavytsky announced this after a meeting with EU Commissioner for Climate Action Connie Hedegaard, which was held in Brussels.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 09:51:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Ex-Head of State Customs Service Makarenko given four-year suspended sentence</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175824</link><description>The Pechersky District Court of Kyiv has found former Head of the State Customs Service of Ukraine Anatoliy Makarenko guilty of abuse of power and office. He was charged with the illegal customs clearance in early 2009 of 11 billion cubic meters of natural gas owned by RosUkrEnergo. The court passed a four-year suspended sentence on him</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 09:38:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Bezuhly: Ukraine not to set quotas on grain exports</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175823</link><description>Quotas on grain exports will not be set this year due to the low yield of grain crops in Ukraine, Ukrainian Deputy Agricultural Policy and Food Minister Mykola Bezuhly has said during his working visit to Odesa region.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 09:29:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>There will be no problems with vegetables this year in Ukraine</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175822</link><description>Such an opinion was expressed by Ukrainian Prime Minister Mykola Azarov during his working visit to Kherson region.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 09:16:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category><enclosure url="http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/_picture/parent/listing/176/148_175822.jpg" length="13056" type="image/jpeg" /></item>
<item><title>Last night due to bad weather blackouts registered in 61 towns in five regions of Ukraine</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175819</link><description>According to the press service of Ministry for Emergencies in Volyn region blackouts occvurred in 31 settlements, in Lviv - 12, in Ivano-Frankivsk - 7 in Cherkassy - 7, in Chernihiv - 4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 09:02:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category><enclosure url="http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/_picture/parent/listing/176/148_175819.jpg" length="11289" type="image/jpeg" /></item>
<item><title>Ukraine, EU finally initial agreement on free trade area</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175816</link><description>Ukraine and the EU have finally completed the technical process of finalizing the text of the section of the association agreement, which concerns the creation of a deep and comprehensive free trade area. The final initialling of the text took place in Brussels.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 08:46:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category><enclosure url="http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/_picture/parent/listing/176/148_175816.jpg" length="13124" type="image/jpeg" /></item>
<item><title>Government set to modernize irrigation networks through concessions</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175815</link><description>This was disclosed by Minister of Agrarian Policy and Food Mykola Prysiazhniuk said in Kherson region who said that currently, the government is taking steps to consolidate the irrigation systems in order to continue their reconstruction and modernization.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>State banks to become locomotive for development of Ukrainian banking system</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175813</link><description>This is what People&apos;s Deputy and Advisor of the Prime Minister Vasyl Horbal has said at a press conference in Ivano-Frankivsk.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 08:18:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Government to implement long-term lands irrigation program</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175812</link><description>This was disclosed by Prime Minister Mykola Azarov when attending the base pumping station of the Main Department of Kakhovka Main Canal in Kherson region.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 08:05:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Foreign markets entered by national agricultural producers should be preserved and increased</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175740</link><description>Agrarian Policy and Food Minister Mykola Prysiazhniuk has said about this during his stay in Kherson region as a member of the government delegation headed by Prime Minister Mykola Azarov.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 11:35:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Ukrainian Environment and Natural Resources Minister to discuss cooperation with EU in environment</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175739</link><description>Ukrainian Environment and Natural Resources Minister Eduard Stavytsky will make a working visit to Brussels on July 19 to discuss current issues of cooperation with the European Union in the field of environmental protection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 11:23:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Ukraine not to set quotas on grain exports</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175737</link><description>Quotas on grain exports will not be set this year due to the low yield of grain crops in Ukraine, Ukrainian Deputy Agricultural Policy and Food Minister Mykola Bezuhly has said. He announced this during his working visit to Odesa region.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 11:01:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Electronic card introduced by Sumy border guards</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175735</link><description>Electronic card containing passport data allows citizens to cross the border while entering Ukraine or leaving it and in specially assigned direction in the shortest period of time, said the spokesperson of the border guard unit Roman Tkach.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 10:41:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Privileges for domestic book publishers not to be cancelled</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175732</link><description>This was voiced by Minister for Education and Science, Youth and Sports Dmytro Tabachnyk who said he knows nothing about the initiative to cancel privileges for domestic book publishers and insists that they be extended.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 10:25:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category><enclosure url="http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/_picture/parent/listing/176/148_175732.jpg" length="13421" type="image/jpeg" /></item>
<item><title>Bondarenko gets off to successful start at WTA Bastad</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175728</link><description>Ukrainian Kateryna Bondarenko, who is preparing for the London Olympics 2012, advanced to the second round of the Women&apos;s Tennis Association (WTA) tournament in Bastad, Sweden, with prize money of USD 220,000.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 10:15:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category><enclosure url="http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/_picture/parent/listing/176/148_175728.jpg" length="13025" type="image/jpeg" /></item>
<item><title>Over 17,000 persons become cictims of road traffic accidents</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175724</link><description>The Prime Minister of Ukraine stressed the priority of ensuring safety of traffic in work of the Interior Ministry and the State Automobile Inspectorate. Mykola Azarov has said about this at the Cabinet&apos;s meeting.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 10:06:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category><enclosure url="http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/_picture/parent/listing/176/148_175724.jpg" length="12679" type="image/jpeg" /></item>
<item><title>&quot;Ukrainian Railways&quot; (Ukrzaliznytsia) to complete reform for seven years</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175720</link><description>But, its privatization is not planned. This was disclosed by Chairman of the State Railway Administration of Ukraine Ukrzaliznytsia Volodymyr Kozak.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 09:55:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category><enclosure url="http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/_picture/parent/listing/176/148_175720.jpg" length="14155" type="image/jpeg" /></item>
<item><title>Prime Minister to check state of water supply in Kherson region</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175717</link><description>This will be done during a working trip of Mykola Azarov during a trip to Kherson region.And during the week officials should develop measures to improve quality of potable water in the locations where it is of poor quality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 09:44:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category><enclosure url="http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/_picture/parent/listing/176/148_175717.jpg" length="13134" type="image/jpeg" /></item>
<item><title>No rise of bread prices expected in Ukraine</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175713</link><description>Prices for grain and wheat will remain at the previous year level in Ukraine.This was aired by First Deputy Agrarian Policy and Food Minister Mykola Bezuhly during his working visit to Odesa region.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 09:03:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Economic growth will continue in Ukraine by end of year</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175712</link><description>President Viktor Yanukovych said this at a meeting with local officials. Head of the State is confident that in the second half of this year the government will fulfill its social obligations as successfully as it did it in the first half of 2012.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 08:50:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Patriarch Kirill to hold prayer service in Kyiv</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175710</link><description>Patriarch of Moscow and All Russia Kirill, during his visit to Ukraine scheduled for July 26-28, will hold a prayer service in Kyiv on July 27 to mark the anniversary of the conversion of the Kyiv Rus to Christianity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 08:42:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Polish Culture and European Dialogue Center to open in Ivano-Frankivsk</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175709</link><description>The Polish Culture Center is supposed to be opened on the second floor of the house on 56, Sichovykh Striltsiv Street. In accordance with the Ivano-Frankivsk City Council&apos;s decision, the lease term is 49 years.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 08:27:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Third of air pollution caused by motor vehicles in Kyiv</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175708</link><description>The air pollution level constantly grows and the city needs ecologically clean transport and bicycles.Such a situation with the use of statistical data is presented by the press service of the Ecology and Natural Resources Ministry.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 08:16:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>All-Ukrainian contest launched by Ukrainian National News Agency</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175707</link><description>The event is part of the School of Young Journalist. The contest &quot;Europe around me&quot; among young people is aimed primarily at the perception of European values by future generations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 08:03:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Quality of potable water to be improved</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175636</link><description>Ministry of Environment and other line agencies should work up measures to improve quality of potable water in the locations where it is of poor quality.This was stressed by Prime Minister Mykola Azarov at a meeting of the Government.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 12:24:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category><enclosure url="http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/_picture/parent/listing/176/148_175636.jpg" length="12679" type="image/jpeg" /></item>
<item><title>MFA of Ukraine to continue working on simplifying travels abroad for Ukrainian citizens</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175629</link><description>This was stressed by Director of Information Policy of the Ministry of Foreign Affairs of Ukraine Oleg Voloshyn.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 12:02:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category><enclosure url="http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/_picture/parent/listing/176/148_175629.jpg" length="12011" type="image/jpeg" /></item>
<item><title>UNICEF Special Prize awarded to film about homeless</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175633</link><description>This film titled &quot;Champions from gateway&quot; was presented at the Odessa International Film Festival as part of Ukrainian national competition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 11:41:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category><enclosure url="http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/_picture/parent/listing/176/148_175633.jpg" length="12321" type="image/jpeg" /></item>
<item><title>Ukrainians prefer holidaying in Turkey and Egypt</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175626</link><description>More than 70 percent of Ukrainians traveling abroad choose Turkey and Egypt for their holidays. The remaining 30 percent choose other countries.This was disclosed by Vice-President of the Association of Leaders of the Tourist Business of Ukraine (ALTU) Oleksandr Novikovsky.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 11:28:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Ukraine intends to tranfer domestic thermal power plants to use of water-coal fuel</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175628</link><description>Ukraine hopes Chinese financial resources will help realize this project. This is what Deputy Minister of Energy and Coal industry Volodymyr Makukha said.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 11:16:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Ukraine to build yearly 100,000 apartments of economy class</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175625</link><description>And every region of the country in future will have plants producing concrete structures for the construction of affordable housing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 10:58:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Ukrainians actively buying up cars</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175621</link><description>Sales in June rose by a quarter compared with the corresponding  figure of the last year.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 10:44:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category><enclosure url="http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/_picture/parent/listing/176/148_175621.jpg" length="14883" type="image/jpeg" /></item>
<item><title>Ukraine and EU finalizing text of association agreement section on FTA</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175619</link><description>Ukraine and the EU have finally completed the technical process of finalizing the text of a section of the association agreement, which concerns the creation of a deep and comprehensive free trade area. The final initialling of the text will take place in Brussels on July 19.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 10:34:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category><enclosure url="http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/_picture/parent/listing/176/148_175619.gif" length="12319" type="image/gif" /></item>
<item><title>Premier says economy of Ukraine continues to grow</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175617</link><description>Despite the negative impact of the global environment and the recession in the European Union, Ukraine&apos;s economy continues to grow.This is what Prime Minister of Ukraine Mykola Azarov said, summing up the first half of this year.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 10:22:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category><enclosure url="http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/_picture/parent/listing/176/148_175617.jpg" length="7791" type="image/jpeg" /></item>
<item><title>Advisory Center for agricultural workers starts work in Ukraine</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175615</link><description>The Advisory Center was created on an initiative of Agrarian Policy and Food Minister Mykola Prysiazhniuk.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 09:14:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Introduction of ban for grain export outside region, initiated in some Ukrainian regions groundless</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175614</link><description>In addition, such a step may lead to reduction in the volume of investments and tell on the dynamics of the agrarian sector development. This opinion was expressed by Agrarian Policy and Food Minister Mykola Prysiazhniuk during his working visit to Cherkasy region.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 09:09:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Grain reserves at Ukrainian farms 2.3 times higher than last year</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175607</link><description>According to the State Statistics Service,Grain reserves at agricultural enterprises in Ukraine as of July 1, totaled 9.8 million tons, 2.3 times more compared to the same date in 2011.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 08:54:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Two Ukrainian pilots killed in Congo helicopter crash</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175606</link><description>Two Ukrainian pilots have been killed after the police helicopter Mi-2 crashed in the Republic of the Congo. The accident took place on July 16 in Mbouambe, a town 180 kilometers north of Congo&apos;s capital, Brazzaville.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 08:41:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Ukrainian Foreign Minister to attend Eastern Partnership Foreign Ministers Meeting</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175605</link><description>Ukraine&apos;s Foreign Minister Kostiantyn Hryshchenko will participate in the 3rd Eastern Partnership Foreign Ministers Meeting on July 23 in Brussels.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 08:27:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Premier demands problem of medicines for children with cancer be solved soon</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175604</link><description>Ukrainian Prime Minister Mykola Azarov has instructed Deputy Prime Minister and Health Minister Raisa Bohatyriova to promptly resolve the issue of providing children&apos;s cancer hospitals with the necessary medicines.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 08:15:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Quality of potable water supply sources worsening in Ukraine</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175549</link><description>This has been discussed at a meeting dedicated to the implementation of the Potable Water of Ukraine state program, chaired by Prime Minister Mykola Azarov in Kyiv.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 12:04:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Ukraine should refuse from using detergents containing phosphates</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175548</link><description>This what experts of the Ministry for Regional Development, Construction and Housing and Utility Services of Ukraine say.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 11:42:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Euro-2012 had positive impact on Ukraine's international image,Martin Kallen says</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175539</link><description>Chief Operating Officer of UEFA Events SA Martin Kallen told this at a final press conference dedicated to EURO 2012, which was held at the Olympic Stadium in Kyiv.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 11:21:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>Male Ukraine National in beach handball wins silver medals at world championship in Oman</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175536</link><description>Brazil bacame gold medal winners of the tournament.Croatia took the broze medals having beaten the Russians.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 11:11:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>
<item><title>UAH 100 million needed for reconstruction of Bortnychi WWTP, Premier says</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175533</link><description>According to Prime Minister Mykola Azarov, the reconstruction of the station has already started.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 10:50:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category><enclosure url="http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/_picture/parent/listing/176/148_175533.jpg" length="8875" type="image/jpeg" /></item>
<item><title>Inventory of objects used by Russian Black Sea Fleet continues in Crimea</title><link>http://www.nrcu.gov.ua/index.php?id=148&amp;listid=175527</link><description>According to State Property Fund Chairman Oleksandr Riabchenko, inventory of real estate objects used by the Russian Black Sea Fleet is held for the first time since the stay of the fleet in Crimea.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 10:38:00 GMT</pubDate><category>News</category></item>

</channel>
</rss>